Guide to the University of Chicago Contemporary Chamber Players Records 1958-2002
University of Chicago Library
- Series XII: Performance and Promotion
  - Subseries 1: Promotional Materials
    - Non-Contemporary Chamber Players Programs and Fliers, 1973-1992 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Programs and program notes, 1963-1965, undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Programs and program notes, 1966-1969 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Programs and program notes, 1970-1974 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Programs and program notes, 1975-1977 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Programs and program notes, 1978-1979 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Programs and program notes, 1980-1985 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Programs and program notes, 1986-1988 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Programs and program notes, 1989-1991 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Programs and program notes, 1992-1996 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Programs and program notes, 1996-1997 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Programs and mailers, 2001-2002 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Program notes copy, 1958-63 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Program notes copy, undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Shapey program notes bio, undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 2: Performance Records
    - Concert master lists, 1964-1974 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Stravinsky's L'Histoire du Soldat Concert, 1966-1968 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Lexington String Quartet, 1967-1970 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Israeli Concert, 1974-1976 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Contemporary Concerts, Inc., 1976-1977 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Shapey's Praise Concert, 1975-1976 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Fromm Birthday Concert, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Scheduling and personnel lists, 1964-69 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Scheduling and personnel lists, 1970-82 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Scheduling and personnel lists, undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Performance and rehearsal paysheets, 1969-87, undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Concert instruments and equipment, 1976, undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Performance instrumentation, 1965-69, undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Performance instrumentation, 1970-76, undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Performance instrumentation, 1977-91, undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Performance Records, 1976-1978 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - General Performance Records, 2002-2003 Season [1 of 2], 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - General Performance Records, 2002-2003 Season [2 of 2], 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Series XIII: Oversize
  This series includes all oversized Contemporary Chamber Players concert posters and photographs, a musical score, and a poster for the Jerusalem Symphony Orchestra conducted by Ralph Shapey. The series spans the years 1964-1982.
  Oversize posters were transferred from Series XII, Subseries 1, while oversize photographs were transferred from Series XI.
  - Performer photographs, 1967, undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Concert posters, 1965-1968 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Jerusalem Symphony Orchestra poster, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Winsor, Phil – "Conflations for Chamber Orchestra" – Score, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Series XIV: Audio and Video
  This series spans the years 1966-1996, and includes audio and video recordings of Contemporary Chamber Players performances, rehearsals, studio sessions, seminars and panels. It also contains recordings of the work of composers with whom Shapey corresponded, and a few tapes intended for use in performances.
  There are two ranges of audio recordings. Each is arranged first by format, and the recordings in boxes 18-47 are then arranged chronologically by recording date. Recordings in boxes 48-54 are arranged alphabetically by composer.
  Formats include 10-inch, 7-inch, and 5-inch diameter reel-to-reel tape, audio cassette, compact disc (CD) and digital audio tape (DAT). Many of the CDs and DATs are reformatted copies of original reel-to-reel tapes in the series; most of the reformatted recordings are of Ralph Shapey's performances with CCP.
  Video recordings are in Beta format, and are organized chronologically in box 47.
  Many of the CDs and DATs are marked with additional sequential numbers; because these number sequences are incomplete and do not represent chronological organization, they have not been documented in the inventory.
  - Item 1: 10 inch reel-to-reel tape, February 11, 1965 interview (Box 18)
  - Item 2: 10 inch reel-to-reel tape, January 11, 1966 interview (Box 18)
  - Item 3: 10 inch reel-to-reel tape, May 26, 1966, panel (Box 18)
  - Items 4-7: 10 inch reel-to-reel tapes, April 11, 1967 performance (Box 18)
  - Items 8-9: 10 inch reel-to-reel tapes, April 23, 1967 panel (Box 18)
  - Items 10-12: 10 inch reel-to-reel tapes, October 10, 1967 performance (Box 18)
  - Items 1-6: 10 inch reel-to-reel tapes, January 26, 1968 performance (Box 19)
  - Item 7: 10 inch reel-to-reel tape, January 28, 1968 performance (Box 19)
  - Item 8-10: 10 inch reel-to-reel tapes, February 23, 1968 performance (Box 19)
  - Item 11: 10 inch reel-to-reel tape, March 1, 1968 performance (Box 19)
  - Items 12-13: 10 inch reel-to-reel tape, January, 24, 1969 performance (Box 19)
  - Items 1-2: 10 inch reel-to-reel tapes, January 17, 1969 performance (Box 20)
  - Items 3-5: 10 inch reel-to-reel tapes, February 28, 1969 performance (Box 20)
  - Items 6-8: 10 inch reel-to-reel tapes, April 18, 1969 performance (Box 20)
  - Items 9-10: 10 inch reel-to-reel tapes, January 23, 1970 performance (Box 20)
  - Items 11-12: 10 inch reel-to-reel tapes, February 27, 1970 performance (Box 20)
  - Items 1-2: 10 inch reel-to-reel tapes, April 3, 1970 performance (Box 21)
  - Items 3-4: 10 inch reel-to-reel tapes, April 10, 1970 performance (Box 21)
  - Items 5-6: 10 inch reel-to-reel tapes, January 22, 1971 performance (Box 21)
  - Item 7: 10 inch reel-to-reel tape, March 5, 1971 performance (Box 21)
  - Item 8: 10 inch reel-to-reel tape, April 23, 1971 performance (Box 21)
  - Item 9: 10 inch reel-to-reel tape, January 14, 1972 performance (Box 21)
  - Item 10: 10 inch reel-to-reel tape, January 21, 1972 performance (Box 21)
  - Item 11: 10 inch reel-to-reel tape, March 3, 1972 performance (Box 21)
  - Item 12: 10 inch reel-to-reel tape, January 26, 1973 performance (Box 21)
  - Item 1: 10 inch reel-to-reel tape, March 2, 1973 performance (Box 22)
  - Item 2: 10 inch reel-to-reel tape, March 6, 1973 performance (Box 22)
  - Item 3: 10 inch reel-to-reel tape, April 13, 1973 performance (Box 22)
  - Item 4: 10 inch reel-to-reel tape, May 25, 1973 performance (Box 22)
  - Item 5: 10 inch reel-to-reel tape, January 21, 1974 performance (Box 22)
  - Item 6: 10 inch reel-to-reel tape, January 28, 1974 performance (Box 22)
  - Item 7: 10 inch reel-to-reel tape, March 8, 1974 performance (Box 22)
  - Items 8-9: 10 inch reel-to-reel tapes, May 24, 1974 performance (Box 22)
  - Item 10: 10 inch reel-to-reel tape, January 23, 1976 rehearsal (Box 22)
  - Item 11: 10 inch reel-to-reel tape, January 24, 1976 performance (Box 22)
  - Items 1-3: 10 inch reel-to-reel tapes, January 27, 1976 performance (Box 23)
  - Item 4: 10 inch reel-to-reel tape, May 9, 1976 performance (Box 23)
  - Items 5-6: 10 inch reel-to-reel tapes, May 28, 1976 performance (Box 23)
  - Items 7-8: 10 inch reel-to-reel tapes, January 20, 1977 rehearsal (Box 23)
  - Item 9: 10 inch reel-to-reel tape, January 21, 1977 performance (Box 23)
  - Items 10-11: 10 inch reel-to-reel tapes, April 22, 1977 performance (Box 23)
  - Item 1: 10 inch reel-to-reel tape, April 29, 1977 performance (Box 24)
  - Items 2-3: 10 inch reel-to-reel tapes, May 19, 1978 performance (Box 24)
  - Items 4-5: 10 inch reel-to-reel tapes, May 20, 1977 performance (Box 24)
  - Items 6-7: 10 inch reel-to-reel tapes, January 20, 1978 performance (Box 24)
  - Items 8-9: 10 inch reel-to-reel tapes, March 3, 1978 performance (Box 24)
  - Items 10-11: 10 inch reel-to-reel tapes, April 14, 1978 performance (Box 24)
  - Items 12-13: 10 inch reel-to-reel tapes, May 25, 1978 performance (Box 24)
  - Item 1: 10 inch reel-to-reel tape, March 9, 1979 performance (Box 25)
  - Items 2-3: 10 inch reel-to-reel tapes, April 20, 1979 performance (Box 25)
  - Items 4-5: 10 inch reel-to-reel tapes, May 25, 1979 performance (Box 25)
  - Items 6-8: 10 inch reel-to-reel tapes, March 10, 1980 performance (Box 25)
  - Items 9-10: 10 inch reel-to-reel tapes, April 24, 1981 performance (Box 25)
  - Items 11-12: 10 inch reel-to-reel tapes, January 22, 1982 performance (Box 25)
  - Items 1-2: 10 inch reel-to-reel tapes, April 16, 1982 performance (Box 26)
  - Item 3: 10 inch reel-to-reel tape, April 22, 1983 performance (Box 26)
  - Item 4: 10 inch reel-to-reel tape, May 27, 1983 performance (Box 26)
  - Items 5-6: 10 inch reel-to-reel tapes, November 19, 1983 performance (Box 26)
  - Item 7: 10 inch reel-to-reel tape, February 10, 1984 performance (Box 26)
  - Item 8: 10 inch reel-to-reel tape, March 3, 1984 performance (Box 26)
  - Item 9: 10 inch reel-to-reel tape, April 27, 1984 performance (Box 26)
  - Items 10-11: 10 inch reel-to-reel tapes, November 21, 1984 performance (Box 26)
  - Item 1: 10 inch reel-to-reel tapes, January 18, 1985 performance (Box 27)
  - Items 2-7: 10 inch reel-to-reel tapes, February 21, 1985 performance (Box 27)
  - Items 8-9: 10 inch reel-to-reel tapes, April 12, 1985 performance (Box 27)
  - Item 10: 10 inch reel-to-reel tape, May 8, 1985 performance (Box 27)
  - Item 11: 10 inch reel-to-reel tape, May 19, 1985 performance (Box 27)
  - Items 1-4: 10 inch reel-to-reel tape, undated performance (Box 28)
  - Item 5: 10 inch reel-to-reel tape, undated conversation (Box 28)
  - Items 6-8: 10 inch reel-to-reel tape, undated studio recording (Box 28)
  - Item 9: April 14, 1972 performance (box only) (Box 28)
  - Item 10: April 19, 1974 performance (box only) (Box 28)
  - Items 1- 9: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, December 4, 1967 performance (Box 29)
  - Items 10-24: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, January 6, 1967 performance (Box 29)
  - Items 25-40: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, January 17, 1967 performance (Box 29)
  - Items 1-13: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, January 24, 1967 performance (Box 30)
  - Items 14-22: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, February 21, 1967 performance (Box 30)
  - Items 23-27: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, April 16, 1967 performance (Box 30)
  - Items 28- 40: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, May 2, 1967 performance (Box 30)
  - Items 1-11: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, April 16, 1967 performance (Box 31)
  - Items 12-13: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, May 2, 1967 performance (Box 31)
  - Items 14-18: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, November 10, 1967 performance (Box 31)
  - Items 19-21: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, November 28, 1967 performance (Box 31)
  - Item 22: 7 inch reel-to-reel tape, December 8, 1967 performance (Box 31)
  - Item 23: 7 inch reel-to-reel tape, January 28, 1968 performance (Box 31)
  - Item 24: 7 inch reel-to-reel tape, March 1, 1967 performance (Box 31)
  - Item 25: 7 inch reel-to-reel tape, May 2, 1967 performance (Box 31)
  - Items 26-28: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, April 19, 1968 performance (Box 31)
  - Item 29: 7 inch reel-to-reel tape, November 8, 1968 performance (Box 31)
  - Items 30-31: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, January 24, 1969 performance (Box 31)
  - Items 32-34: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, February 28, 1969 performance (Box 31)
  - Items 35-36: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, March 16, 1969 performance (Box 31)
  - Items 37-39: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, April 18, 1969 performance (Box 31)
  - Items 40-42: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, January 2, 1970 performance (Box 31)
  - Items 43-45: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, February 27, 1970 performance (Box 31)
  - Items 1-7: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, February 27, 1970 performance (Box 32)
  - Items 8-10: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, April 3, 1970 performance (Box 32)
  - Items 11-14: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, April 10, 1970 performance (Box 32)
  - Items 16-17: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, April 24, 1970 performance (Box 32)
  - Items 18-19: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, June 1, 1970 performance (Box 32)
  - Items 20-21: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, January 22, 1971 performance (Box 32)
  - Item 22: 7 inch reel-to-reel tape, January 22, 1971 rehearsal (Box 32)
  - Items 23-25: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, March 5, 1971 performance (Box 32)
  - Items 26-31: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, March 7, 1971 seminar (Box 32)
  - Items 32-36: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, April 23, 1971 performance (Box 32)
  - Item 37: 7 inch reel-to-reel tape, May 21, 1971 performance (Box 32)
  - Items 1-3: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, May 21, 1971 performance (Box 33)
  - Items 4-6: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, January 14, 1972 performance (Box 33)
  - Items 7-8: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, January 15, 1972 seminar (Box 33)
  - Items 9-13: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, January 21, 1972 performance (Box 33)
  - Items 14-15: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, March 3, 1972 performance (Box 33)
  - Items 16-19: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, April 14, 1972 performance (Box 33)
  - Items 20-23: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, May 26, 1972 performance (Box 33)
  - Items 24-25: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, February 24, 1973 seminar (Box 33)
  - Items 26: 7 inch reel-to-reel tape, March 2, 1973 performance (Box 33)
  - Items 27-29: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, April 8, 1973 seminar (Box 33)
  - Items 31-32: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, December 7, 1974 seminar (Box 33)
  - Items 33-36: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, January 24, 1975 performance (Box 33)
  - Item 1: 7 inch reel-to-reel tape, January 29, 1975 performance (Box 34)
  - Items 2-7: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, March 6, 1975 rehearsal (Box 34)
  - Items 8-14: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, April 11, 1975 performance (Box 34)
  - Items 15-18: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, May 30, 1975 performance (Box 34)
  - Item 19: 7 inch reel-to-reel tape, June 8, 1975 performance (Box 34)
  - Items 20-21: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, January 24, 1976 performance (Box 34)
  - Items 22-23: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, January 24, 1976 performance (Box 34)
  - Items 24-25: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, April 9, 1979 performance (Box 34)
  - Items 26-27: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, May 28, 1976 performance (Box 34)
  - Items 28-29: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, January 21, 1977 performance (Box 34)
  - Items 1-3: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, March 5, 1977 performance (Box 35)
  - Item 4: 7 inch reel-to-reel tape, April 22, 1977 performance (Box 35)
  - Item 5: 7 inch reel-to-reel tape, May 20, 1977 performance (Box 35)
  - Items 6-8: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, January 20, 1978 performance (Box 35)
  - Items 9-10: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, April 3, 1978 performance (Box 35)
  - Items 11-13: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, April 14, 1978 performance (Box 35)
  - Items 14-16: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, May 16, 1978 performance (Box 35)
  - Items 17-20: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, March 9, 1979 performance (Box 35)
  - Items 21-23: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, April 20, 1979 performance (Box 35)
  - Items 24-28: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, February 29, 1980 performance (Box 35)
  - Items 29-30: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, March 10, 1980 performance (Box 35)
  - Items 31-32: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, January 22, 1982 performance (Box 35)
  - Items 1-2: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, April 16, 1982 performance (Box 36)
  - Item 3: 7 inch reel-to-reel tape, April 16, 1982 performance (Box 36)
  - Item 4: 7 inch reel-to-reel tape, November 21, 1984 performance (Box 36)
  - Items 5-7: 7 inch reel-to-reel tapes, February 1, 1987 performance (Box 36)
  - Item 8: 7 inch reel-to-reel tape, March 6, 1987 performance (Box 36)
  - Item 9: 7 inch reel-to-reel tape, April 24, 1987 performance (Box 36)
  - Item 10: 7 inch reel-to-reel tape, May 19, 1987 performance (Box 36)
  - Item 11: 7 inch reel-to-reel tape, November 4, 1989 performance (Box 36)
  - Items 12-15: 5 inch reel-to-reel tapes, January 23, 1970 performance (Box 36)
  - Item 16: 5 inch reel-to-reel tape, January 21, 1972 performance (Box 36)
  - Item 17: 5 inch reel-to-reel tape, May 26, 1972 performance (Box 36)
  - Item 1: Audio cassette, January 24, 1976 performance (Box 37)
  - Item 2: Audio cassette, January 13, 1984 performance (Box 37)
  - Item 3: Audio cassette, February 1, 1987 performance (Box 37)
  - Item 4: Audio cassette, March 3, 1987 performance (Box 37)
  - Item 5: Audio cassette, November 22, 1987 performance (Box 37)
  - Item 6: Audio cassette, December 4, 1987 performance (Box 37)
  - Item 7: Audio cassette, March 4, 1988 performance (Box 37)
  - Items 8-9: Audio cassettes, April 22, 1988 performance (Box 37)
  - Item 10: Audio cassette, May 20, 1988 performance (Box 37)
  - Item 11: Audio cassette, April 21, 1989 performance (Box 37)
  - Item 12: Audio cassette, May 19, 1989 performance (Box 37)
  - Item 13: Audio cassette, March 2, 1990 performance (Box 37)
  - Item 14: Audio cassette, May 17, 1991 performance (Box 37)
  - Items 15-17 Audio cassettes, January 26, 1992 performance (Box 37)
  - Item 1: Audio cassette, February 7, 1992 performance (Box 38)
  - Item 2: Audio cassette, March 6, 1992 performance (Box 38)
  - Items 3-4: Audio cassettes, April 24, 1992 performance (Box 38)
  - Items 5-6: Audio cassettes, May 22, 1992 performance (Box 38)
  - Items 7-9: Audio cassettes, January 24, 1993 performance (Box 38)
  - Item 10: Audio cassette, February 7, 1993 performance (Box 38)
  - Item 11: Audio cassette, February 28, 1993 performance (Box 38)
  - Items 12-13: Audio cassettes, April 23, 1993 performance (Box 38)
  - Items 14-15: Audio cassettes, May 22, 1994 performance (Box 38)
  - Item 1: Audio cassette, April 2, 1995 performance (Box 39)
  - Item 2: Audio cassette, April 2, 1995 discussion (Box 39)
  - Item 3: Audio cassette, May 19, 1995 performance (Box 39)
  - Item 4: Audio cassette, May 19, 1995 performance (Box 39)
  - Item 5: Audio cassette, June 2, 1995 performance (Box 39)
  - Item 6: DAT, December 4, 1966 performance (Box 39)
  - Item 7: DAT, January 6, 1967 performance (Box 39)
  - Item 8: DAT, January 17, 1967 performance (Box 39)
  - Item 9: DAT, January 24, 1967 performance (Box 39)
  - Item 10: DAT, February 21, 1967 performance (Box 39)
  - Item 11: DAT, April 11, 1967 performance (Box 39)
  - Item 12: DAT, April 16, 1967 performance (Box 39)
  - Item 13: DAT, May 2, 1967 performance (Box 39)
  - Item 14: DAT, October 10, 1967 performance (Box 39)
  - Item 15: DAT, November 28, 1967 performance (Box 39)
  - Item 16: DAT, December 8, 1967 performance (Box 39)
  - Item 17: DAT, January 26, 1968 performance (Box 39)
  - Item 18: DAT, February 23, 1968 performance (Box 39)
  - Item 19: DAT, March 1, 1968 performance (Box 39)
  - Item 20: DAT, April 19, 1968 performance (Box 39)
  - Item 21: DAT, January 17, 1969 performance (Box 39)
  - Item 22: DAT, January 24, 1969 performance (Box 39)
  - Item 1: DAT, March 16, 1969 performance (Box 40)
  - Item 2: DAT, April 18, 1969 performance (Box 40)
  - Item 3: DAT, April 22, 1994 performance (Box 40)
  - Item 4: DAT, January 23, 1970 performance (Box 40)
  - Item 5: DAT, February 27, 1970 performance (Box 40)
  - Item 6: DAT, March 1, 1970 performance (Box 40)
  - Item 7: DAT, April 3, 1970 performance (Box 40)
  - Item 8: DAT, April 10, 1970 performance (Box 40)
  - Item 9: DAT, April 24, 1970 performance (Box 40)
  - Item 10: DAT, June 1, 1970 performance (Box 40)
  - Item 11: DAT, January 22, 1971 performance (Box 40)
  - Item 12: DAT, March 5, 1971 performance (Box 40)
  - Item 13: DAT, April 23, 1971 performance (Box 40)
  - Item 14: DAT, May 21, 1971 performance (Box 40)
  - Item 15: DAT, January 14, 1972 performance (Box 40)
  - Item 16: DAT, January 15, 1972 seminar (Box 40)
  - Item 17: DAT, January 21, 1972 performance (Box 40)
  - Item 18: DAT, March 3, 1972 performance (Box 40)
  - Item 19: DAT, April 14, 1972 performance (Box 40)
  - Item 20: DAT, May 26, 1972 performance (Box 40)
  - Item 21: DAT, January 26, 1973 performance (Box 40)
  - Item 22: DAT, February 24, 1973 performance (Box 40)
  - Item 23: DAT, March 2, 1973 performance (Box 40)
  - Item 24: DAT, March 6, 1973 performance (Box 40)
  - Item 25 DAT, April 8, 1973 performance (Box 40)
  - Item 26: DAT, April 13, 1973 performance (Box 40)
  - Item 27: DAT, May 25, 1973 performance (Box 40)
  - Item 28: DAT, January 28, 1974 performance (Box 40)
  - Item 1: DAT, February 21, 1974 performance (Box 41)
  - Item 2: DAT, March 8, 1974 performance (Box 41)
  - Item 3: DAT, April 21, 1974 performance (Box 41)
  - Item 4: DAT, December 7, 1974 performance (Box 41)
  - Item 5: DAT, January 24, 1975 performance (Box 41)
  - Item 6: DAT, March 7, 1975 performance (Box 41)
  - Item 7: DAT, April11, 1975 performance (Box 41)
  - Item 8: DAT, May 30, 1975 performance (Box 41)
  - Item 9: DAT, June 8, 1975 performance (Box 41)
  - Item 10: DAT, April 9, 1976 performance (Box 41)
  - Item 11: DAT, May 28 1976 performance (Box 41)
  - Item 12: DAT, March 5, 1977 performance (Box 41)
  - Item 13: DAT, April 22, 1977 performance (Box 41)
  - Item 14: DAT, April 29, 1977 performance (Box 41)
  - Item 15: DAT, May 20, 1977 performance (Box 41)
  - Item 16: DAT, January 20, 1978 performance (Box 41)
  - Item 17: DAT, March 3, 1978 performance (Box 41)
  - Item 18: DAT, April 14, 1978 performance (Box 41)
  - Item 19: DAT, May 19, 1978 performance (Box 41)
  - Item 11: DAT, May 25, 1978 performance (Box 41)
  - Item 12: DAT, March 9, 1979 performance (Box 41)
  - Item 13: DAT, April 20, 1979 performance (Box 41)
  - Item 14: DAT, February 29, 1980 performance (Box 41)
  - Item 15: DAT, March 10, 1980 performance (Box 41)
  - Item 16: DAT, April 24, 1981 performance (Box 41)
  - Item 1: DAT, January 22, 1982 performance (Box 42)
  - Item 2: DAT, April 22, 1983 performance (Box 42)
  - Item 3: DAT, May 27, 1983 performance (Box 42)
  - Item 4: DAT, October 19, 1983 performance (Box 42)
  - Item 5: DAT, February 10, 1984 performance (Box 42)
  - Item 6: DAT, March 2, 1984 performance (Box 42)
  - Item 7: DAT, May 18, 1984 performance (Box 42)
  - Item 8: DAT, January 18, 1985 performance (Box 42)
  - Item 9: DAT, May 19, 1985 performance (Box 42)
  - Item 10: DAT, March 6, 1987 performance (Box 42)
  - Item 11: DAT, October 4, 1987 performance (Box 42)
  - Item 12: DAT, April 23, 1993 performance (Box 42)
  - Item 13: DAT, January 21, 1994 performance (Box 42)
  - Item 14: DAT, February 25, 1994 performance (Box 42)
  - Item 15: DAT, April 22, 1994 performance (Box 42)
  - Item 16: DAT, May 20, 1994 performance (Box 42)
  - Item 17: DAT, May 16, 1996 performance (Box 42)
  - Items 1-2: CDs, December 4, 1966 performance (Box 43)
  - Item 3: CD, January 6, 1967 performance (Box 43)
  - Items 4-5: CDs, January 17, 1967 performance (Box 43)
  - Items 6-7: CDs, January 24, 1967 performance (Box 43)
  - Items 8-9: CDs, February 21, 1967 performance (Box 43)
  - Item 10: CD, April 11, 1967 performance (Box 43)
  - Items 11-12: CDs, April 16, 1967 performance (Box 43)
  - Item 13: CD, May 2, 1967 performance (Box 43)
  - Items 14-15: CDs, October 10, 1967 performance (Box 43)
  - Item 16: CD, December 8, 1967 performance (Box 43)
  - Item 17: CD, November 28, 1967 performance (Box 43)
  - Item 18: CD, January 28, 1968 performance (Box 43)
  - Item 19: CD, February 28, 1968 performance (Box 43)
  - Item 20: CD, March 1, 1968 performance (Box 43)
  - Item 21: CD, April 19, 1968 performance (Box 43)
  - Items 22-23: CDs, January 17, 1969 performance (Box 43)
  - Item 24: CD, January 24, 1969 performance (Box 43)
  - Item 25: CD, January 24, 1969 performance (Box 43)
  - Item 26: CD, March 16, 1969 performance (Box 43)
  - Item 27: CD, April 18, 1969 performance (Box 43)
  - Items 1-2: CDs, January 23, 1970 performance (Box 44)
  - Items 3-4: CDs, February 27, 1970 performance (Box 44)
  - Item 5: CD, (February or March 1967), studio recording (Box 44)
  - Item 6: CD, April 3, 1970 performance (Box 44)
  - Item 7: CD, April 10, 1970 performance (Box 44)
  - Item 8: CD, April 24, 1970 performance (Box 44)
  - Item 9: CD, June 1, 1970 performance (Box 44)